<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VPT#012-RYP</string>
    <string name="anleitung">Welcome to Rate Your Pics, an app that allows you to rate your pictures very quickly.\n\nYou rate between ★☆☆☆☆ and ★★★★★. The stars will be added as prefix to the filename for easy sorting in any other program or file manager. ☆☆☆☆☆ moves the picture to trash (undo possible during session). That way you will have a clean and quality sorted collection in a very short time. With ← →  you can go back and forth (and also change your mind and re-rate during a session or skip a rating). ↺ takes you back to this screen to select a new folder.\n\nTo toggle overlay display of stars (after rating) on and off, long-tap the picture in the rating screen.\n\nTo start, tap the big red button below \"Select Folder\", select folder and give permissions.\n\n<b><font color="#efcac2">Your data are yours. Everything is calculated and saved locally. Nothing is sent.</font></b>\n\nGifted to you by Valentin ❤️</string>


    <string name="LICENSE">
        Copyright 2024 Valentin\'s PowerTools\n\nThis program is free software: you can redistribute it and/or modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License as published by the Free Software Foundation, either version 3 of the License, or (at your option) any later version.

    This program is distributed in the hope that it will be useful, but WITHOUT ANY WARRANTY; without even the implied warranty of MERCHANTABILITY or FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. See the GNU General Public License for more details.

    You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License along with this program. If not, see\nhttps://www.gnu.org/licenses.\n\nHere is the github link:\nhttps://github.com/v4lpt/RYP

    </string>
    <string name="copy">Copyright and License Information</string>

    <string name="infobuttontextforblinds">Information Button (gives you Information)</string>
    <string name="powertools">Valentin\'s PowerTools #012</string>
    <string name="app_name_show">Rate Your Pics</string>
    <string name="rate_your_pigs">Rate Your Pigs</string>
</resources>